

Sumit Singh

Executive

Contact

Address Gurgaon , India 122002

Phone 9992053612

E-mail sumitsingh0674@gmail.com

Skills

Excellent Communication

Flexible and Adaptable

SAP PowerBuilder

Salesforce.com

Team Work

A Customer Service Assistant with years of experience in a fast-paced corporate environment combining award-winning customer service with the ability to prioritize heavy workload on a daily basis. Excellent interpersonal and communication skills, both verbal and written. An ability to handle highly confidential material on a regular basis. Flexible and able to learn with ease any personalized computer program/all other equipment, and rules/regulations a new work environment may have.

Work History

2020-09 -2022-05

Customer Service Chat Representative

Concentrix Pvt Ltd, Gurgaon

- Asked open-ended questions to determine which products or services would be best fit for customer's needs.
- Worked closely with each customer to carefully resolve issues within timely fashion.
- Responded to customer inquiries and provided accurate information about products and services via live chat.

2022-05 -Current

Email Support Representative

Taskus Pvt Ltd, Gurgaon

- Deployed problem solving, analytics and intuitive skills and offered productive solutions that met customer needs.
- Identified and implemented correct solutions to client issues first-time around within established time limits.
- Built trusting relationships with clients through open and honest communication.

Education

2019-07 - **Bachelor Of Arts** 2022-06 Sabarmati University

2018-04 - Hight School Education : Science Education

Hari Bhoomi Public School

Interests

Music

Travel

Agriculture